hey what's up everybody in this video I
want to show you how to create your own
sixf figure online membership that
includes coaching courses that people
can pay you for that you can earn six
figures from consistently for those of
you that haven't met me yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and I have built
multiple coaching training and
membership businesses over $20 million
per year for the last 21 years and every
single week I help coaches mentors and
trainers scale their businesses online
just like you those that are just
starting out to reach these kind of
results now what I want to do is I want
to walk you through the process if maybe
you're just starting out and you want to
get results with a membership site or
you want to create a coaching program
and all the little nuances that are
involved with that a lot of people think
that what's most important is the topic
that you're going to use and there's a
few processes that make that really
simple to do one of those that I love is
using chat GPT so I'm going to show you
just real quick some of the different
chat GPT prompts that we like to use
this is the process I've worked with
with all of my clients that have gotten
them the most results that can help you
as well my clients have been able to
make tens of thousands of dollars by
working through these different
processes together so in chat GPT right
here if you don't have a chat GPT
account make sure that you get one by
having chat GPT you can brainstorm
various ideas to help you come up with
what to do in your business so right
here I can type in okay uh what are 20
ideas for a membership site I can charge
money for okay and so this is just kind
of a baseline idea you could do a hub of
courses you could do a wellness club
investment advice Content Library
virtual book club creative arts Tech and
gadgets things like that so these are
some various different ideas one of the
first things that you want to really
come up with is what is the thing that
you can help other people do better than
anybody else and you might say well
Jeremiah I'm not better than other
people and so this is why you got to
start to get your mindset in order by
having your mind thinking in a way that
is positive and excited and that you
have a high level of self-esteem and a
high level of self belief in yourself
this is going to tap you right into the
energy that you need that's going to
attract people to you and come up with
the best ideas for you to be able to
create a business like this you got to
really learn to believe in yourself and
that's one of the first stages as far as
this goes that I tell everybody now from
here what we can do is we can pick one
or two of the ideas let's say that you
want to do music lessons let's take this
right here okay um give me 20 sub niches
of music lessons membership okay so chat
gbt can help you come up with some of
this let's say that you not just want to
do music lessons you want to do rock
guitar Mastery I like that one now let's
take this right here I'm going to stop
this by the way you can stop chat jpt by
pressing the stop button uh map out 20
ideas for rock guitar Mastery this is
one of my favorite ways of using chat
GPT is having it come up with a variety
of different ideas based around what we
came up with right here okay so now map
out some courses that some courses that
could be included in a membership like
this okay so right there it's able to
kind of come up with some of the course
ideas that we might use later let's
see here we go okay here's some of the
course
uh guitar fundamentals Rock technique
introduction intermediate courses and
that's a good thing to do is to do like
beginner and intermediate courses inside
of my program the client growth
accelerator program which is our Premier
coaching program where we help coaches
mentors membership site owners be able
to scale their businesses and get the
kind of results that they want we have a
variety of different stuff for beginners
as well as intermediate as well as
experts that have already been in there
okay so this gives you some ideas as far
as how to come up with what idea to pick
once you have your idea and by the way
one of the things I encourage people to
do as well is pick multiple ideas and
let's kind of combine them together
let's kind of bring some of those
together maybe you want to do a specific
age demographic or a certain struggle
that people have now we can build a
program around this and now it's time to
start to put the wheels in motion to
make this come together okay and so one
of the first tools that I love to use is
over here at thinkific dcom thinkific
dcom is the tool that I use when it
comes to building out a membership site
or selling courses online so this allows
you to actually create the membership
this allows you to create the course
platform the learning platform and help
you reach the kind of people that you
are trying to reach this allows you to
deliver the content to people as well I
use this as well to be able to sell
access to what I'm doing where people
can pay you for the things that you're
offering so think giic is one of those
platforms there's a few other great
platforms out there but this is the one
that I use now once you have that what
is the process of actually creating
something like this well a membership is
going to include a number of different
things you can include some courses you
can include access to you we can include
live calls and we can include a
community so these are kind of the four
pillars of a membership that I like to
put together as far as this goes and
then we can pick a price point by the
way I've seen a number of different
price points anywhere from $7 a month
upward to $300 a month as far as this
goes for for my program we're right here
right in the kind of the middle um upper
middle
$197 a month the reason why is we
literally give you everything nuts and
bolt start to finish on how to
successfully build one of these
businesses make the kind of money that
you want to make reach the kind of
people that you want to reach how to
Market and sell everything to get the
results that you want and and I'm
actually there with you personally
walking you through the whole process
I'm there helping you guiding you
directing you I'm there to get support
from to ask questions from in all of
this and I've been doing this for 21
years and so you know that it work works
when you work with me okay so that's why
people really love to get this from me
for
$197 but this is where people I think
they get stuck like well what should I
actually put into it so if we brainstorm
some of those ideas that's great but
this is kind of the rule of thumb that I
look for is you can provide the access
to you this is where they get access to
be able to ask you questions or work
with you or they get access to strategic
content from you they get access to be
able to get your feedback on things lot
classes this is where you get to join
them on like Zoom calls or live streams
and things like that that are exclusive
only for members and then this right
here is community this is where they get
to interact with other people that are
around a similar ideal so this is why
this is different than just creating a
digital product or a course is that I
like to include uh uh multiple courses
inside of that that's already
pre-recorded people can access that they
can log in and they can see that we have
a whole members area people can log in
and set up my my membership where they
can find all of this but we also include
a Facebook group we also include live
Zoom calls we also include a number of
different ways that they can interact
and get their an their questions
answered okay so like right here you can
see we got my learning library we have
start here monthly training calls uh
intermediate courses beginner courses
free webinars archive these are all the
different ways that people can interact
and they get all of these different
pieces of content when they log in here
such as here's one that we're actually
doing right now creating a worldclass
digital course course this is one of our
best courses we just started all about
how to actually record and create a
course we also have um irresistible
offers that sell we have strategic
funnels Made Simple lots of different
ways that we help people and work with
people inside of my program okay so from
here what we can do is this is what
we're going to offer people now we got
to actually learn how to Market it and
you might be saying wait a sec what
about creating all of this and that's
the mistake that most people make when
they're starting out is they try to
create all this stuff I would map this
out in a Google doc first off that's one
of the first things that you want to do
and then I would look out what are maybe
like one the very first course that we
want to make and then map out the next
three to four that we might want to make
but don't create all three or four of
them don't even create the first one
just start recording the first lesson
launch it get people in there and tell
them that these next ones are upcoming
that they're coming soon and that's one
of the best things that you can do to
get things going is by casting vision
for where you're headed what you're
creating and it also puts a little bit
of a fire under you to actually get
stuff going and actually get the ball
rolling as far as that goes okay so what
we want to do is we want to Encompass
with people the transformation that
they're going to get and that's one of
the number one things people don't buy
into information they buy
transformation they buy the promised
result that you're going to get and so
that takes building trust with them what
you want to do is you want to find find
people that are at a specific stage in
their life where what you can help them
with can solve a specific problem and so
you're able to identify what that
specific problem is but we go deeper
than just the information we actually
provide a complete system that lets
people reach those results and we end up
owning that outcome so then what I like
to do is I like to encourage us to take
my three-step process which is
find promote
and then the most important which is
close as in closing the sale getting
people to buy into the thing that you're
offering okay so we're going to find the
people this that are out there we know
where they congregate we're going to
create marketing materials that are
going to attract them to us we're going
to create some sales copy as far as this
goes and we can use AI to help us
brainstorm a lot of these different
things with the sales copy I love doing
this is one of my number one things that
we Mentor my clients on is how to do
that we then go out there and we end up
promoting the thing that we are are
going to use to find the people okay so
to be able to find the people we got to
create a landing page we got to create a
page that actually tells people about
what it is that the membership is going
to offer and so that's really the next
stage that I tell everybody to go on is
to kind of create that page once we
promote it we can do this with social
media content we can do this through
advertising and then we got to know how
to close the sale how to communicate in
in a way that gets people to take action
as far as that goes so if you're just
starting out I'm sure you're wondering
well how do I create all these different
pages and how do I put all this together
again you can use Simple Sites like
think ific to create the the um members
area and then you can use a site like I
use uh personally I use Squarespace to
actually create the landing pages as far
as this goes to reach people um with the
information as far as what it is that
we're offering them okay so all of this
comes together very simply very easily
and you're able to use this to
communicate with people what it is that
you're going to offer that way now once
we go to promote it let's say it's
through social media or you get on a
podcast you do something like that you
have something that you can send people
to that is going to get them to buy into
it they're going to first mentally buy
into it they're going to they're going
to come to you and they're going be like
oh that's exactly what I've been looking
for they're going to find your content
and you're going to have an offer that's
going to get them to take action with
you so that's really the most important
thing is to start to put that offer
together and that's exactly what I love
to help people with in our client growth
accelerator program is to actually put
that offer together the elements of an
effective offer break down as follows
okay number
one we have a paid offer this is what
you're going to charge money for the
problem is is that just support just
promoting a paid offer to people isn't
going to be very effective and so like
if you watch a video like this and I'm
just saying go buy my thing like you're
not going to just go buy from me
anything just cuz you're watching video
for me so you got to build trust and I
got to build trust with people before
they become clients of M we don't we
don't buy into things on the internet
anymore simply because it looks like a
good idea we got to do our research we
got to know is this what I want and the
people that are buying from you exactly
know that as well and they also might be
comparing it to other things that
they've been a part of maybe they've
been disappointed before by other things
so what you got to do is you got to
demonstrate to people that you are
better than all the other things that
they found that are out there and that
you actually can deliver on what your
promises are so the way that we do that
is we use we use mechanisms called a
free offer right here okay so a free
offer is some kind of a mechanism could
be an ebook could be a video training
can be a live uh webinar event to where
you are providing people with some level
of value in exchange for a
name email address
and optionally a phone number okay so
you so they give you this information
and there's a differentiator between
free content and something that they
actually have to register for that's a
free offer let me explain this is a
piece of free content right here you
didn't have to give me any information
to be able to find this video it's free
on
YouTube but there's also no commitment a
lot of people that watch this they're
not going to do anything with what I
talk about but those that actually take
action maybe those that subscribe to my
Channel and they get other videos from
me they might watch more of my videos
then from there I have various free
trainings and live events that I host
you might see an advertisement that I
put out there I might mention it on
another training now I'm going to ask
you to sign up for it with your name and
email address to get access to a deeper
level of content with me to get a deeper
level of access okay so this is what we
got to put together is we got to put
together something where people sign up
and they register for it to get a deeper
level of access with you the reason for
this is to build trust so that you can
lead people right over here to the thing
that you are going to charge money for
so we don't come out the gate even with
our free content and tell people about
the thing that we're charging money for
we use a free offer that way it provides
value it builds trust and you get some
contact information from somebody to be
able to do that we can then use our our
lowcost advertising tools to be able to
market the thing that we have that is
paid over here okay and so that's the
process that I walk people through as I
show them how do we create these
marketing materials how do we put those
together the number one thing that you
want to create is you want to create
some kind of a free offer that is is
they're going to get something of value
from you over here on a lead magnet okay
so a lead magnet has three main elements
it has
a
headline it has a story and it has
a what I
call what's it include that's a you know
maybe we'll come up with a better name
for that one but what's in it as far as
that goes so you don't want to lead with
what's it include you want that to be
the last thing that you talk about you
want to lead with an attention grabbing
headline of some kind that gets people's
attention and then that gets them to buy
into the story of what they are going to
experience after they sign up for or
they become a member okay after they buy
the course after they buy the program
then you tell them what is included in
it over here from here this is where
people get to make a decision as to do I
buy it or do I register for this free
thing is it going to be worth my time or
not now here's the cool part about this
is that when we use social media the
algorithms get to find us the right
people that are looking for this by
training the AI in the algorithm to
actually look for more people that are
wanting the thing that we have to offer
and again in my client growth
accelerator program I walk people
through that whole process of being able
to do that how do we use Facebook ads to
do that how do we we use Instagram ads
to be able to do that when you can learn
to communicate in a way that connects
with people and draws them into the
thing that you're offering they want to
take action with you so we use language
and we use visuals you can use stock
images you can use AI generated images
even to be able to tell the story that
then pulls people in to the thing and
the result and the outcome that they
want we want to keep it very simple you
don't want to go too above and beyond as
far as that goes like I'm working on a
landing page right now this is not
complete yet on my website but it's for
an offer that I'm putting together and
and just some simple words let's get you
more leads with Facebook ads for sixf
fig coaching or course business on
autopilot plugs into an existing
business no complicated Tech no DMS no
sales calls no grinding all day on
social media no high ticket and that's a
huge thing that I love to tell people is
we're not even doing a bunch of high
ticket stuff we actually can help you
build a six and seven figure business
with low ticket or low entry products
that aren't hard to sell that you can
feel confident in and then how to uh put
all this together to find Qualified paid
people that are begging to work with you
as far as that goes so that's that's a
tentative page that I put together this
is some of the language that I'm
starting with to be able to do this to
reach the right people has a little bit
about me right here and then people can
register on this page it's not live
right now but once it is you can go
check that out and maybe you'll see some
advertisements about it in the future or
we'll talk about it on a future video
okay so the goal of that is I want to
connect with people that they want to
learn how to use these methods to be
able to get more clients you can find a
lot of the different videos that I put
out there and because in my accelerator
program that's exactly what we work with
people on is we work with them through
how to make their advertisements work
how to make their campaigns work and how
to get the most results with what
they're offering to people so it starts
with the ability to communicate with
people well it starts with the ability
to connect with people well and so maybe
you're watching this right now and
you're like I don't feel confident in
being able to do this I've never done
this before this is something that's
brand new for me how do I grow in that
confidence how do I have the confidence
that you have Jeremiah well that's
something that I love to teach people
one of the number one things is this is
to believe in yourself number two learn
to calm your nervous system down if
you're operating a fight ORF flight all
the time that's one of the things that
you really want to be aware of because
what that's going to do is you're going
to second guess yourself a lot and
you're going to struggle to be able to
communicate in a way that's effective or
that connects with people one of the
things that I love to do is I love to
meditate Cal nervous system down and
then I can show up with joy and
happiness and excitement when I'm
talking with people I don't even use a
lot of notes when I'm talking because
I'm so connected in my brain that I that
I know exactly what I'm going to say
while I'm communicating I don't need a
whole outliner necessarily like that I
set the intention and then I can talk
and communicate by getting into a flow
State that's one of the number one
things that I love to teach people and
love to walk them through as well okay
so some of this might sound like rocket
science you might say I don't know how
to do all this I don't know how to put
all this together the good news is you
don't have to have it all figured out
when you can learn very simple
strategies you can learn how to put all
these pieces together so like I
mentioned Squarespace landing page like
I mentioned using chat GPT these are two
tools that chat GPT is free that you can
use to brainstorm great ideas we have
some prompts even that you can use that
you can get for free over at my website
over at jerem Kowski decom I have this
thing it's called the free chat GPT
prompt download docent and these are
some of the best prompts that I love to
use when coming up with sales copy and
coming up with sales letters that can
help you come up with some really great
ideas when it comes to your copy and
writing certain things as far as that
goes okay so be sure to check that out
as well this will save you hours and
hours of wondering what to put in your
chat TPT content and all of that over on
your website as well okay now you don't
need to have an elaborate website
websites are kind of a thing of the past
what you want is you want to have a
funnel and you want to have some way of
getting people in that are the right
people so you want to attract the right
people to you by communicating with a
headline and the story element of who it
is and then what we do is we funnel
people down by building trust with them
okay so people might come in at the top
of this funnel right here this might be
your social media content but now they
might sign up for a free offer right
here and maybe they might sign up for a
a lowc cost paid offer right here $27
and then later they might sign up for
something that's like you know $497 or
even you could do it for $47 a month a
membership this by the way is a common
price point that a lot of my clients do
they do something between 27 to $47 a
month to get the ball rolling and then
eventually they might have this as a
beta test number they upgrade it up to
$97 a month okay by doing that you can
get couple hundred people in there and
have a sixf figure business easily if
you just get a 100 people at 97 $ a
month that is a sixf figure business if
you get 50
people at $197 a month that's a six
figure business okay so we don't need to
reinvent the wheel we don't need to do a
lot of hard things we just have to learn
how to stay consistent at attracting the
right people connecting with them
showing up where people are at and then
delivering the results that we promis to
people now you might say Jeremiah I
don't feel confident in being able to
deliver results to people I want you to
learn this you can learn the skill of
delivering results to people it's a
I've had to learn it I didn't know how
to do it years ago I didn't know how to
communicate well with people and now
I've learned how to do so and so that's
something that I'd love to work with you
with I'd love to walk you through that
whole process that I work with people on
is how to develop the skills that they
need how to communicate effectively how
to Market well to people and then
ultimately how do we sell well to people
and what this creates is this creates
consistency in your income this
increases your
impact and what you get to do is you get
to show up not in a sporadic way but you
get to show up
confidently in your business and
ultimately
confidently even if you can't spell or
write like I
did that then what this creates this
creates Financial freedom for you and
time freedom and by being able to bring
the skills the communication ability
your marketing ability and sales ability
together to be able to create the impact
consistency and show up confidently in
your business you truly can create a
business out of a membership site out of
a coaching program out of a course that
brings people together with you that
gets them to want to take action with
you and purchase the thing that you have
to offer and so that's exactly what I
work with people with in my client
growth accelerator program I'd love to
have you in there you can go find that
over at my website jeremy.com you can
find it in the link below and we can
talk more about that all right so listen
this has been a a super quick fast-paced
overview of what it takes to basically
create a membership create a course put
it all together the nuances of the
technical aspects are actually a lot
easier than they seem to create as far
as that goes you create an account you
put it together you put the content in
there and then you start getting clients
we can get so caught up in the weeds of
what are all the stuff that we need to
do what are all the things that I don't
know how to do
yet take it one step at a time come up
with your name come up with the idea map
out a few of those with chat GPT and
then go create an account with something
like think ific to start to put some
things together as far as it goes maybe
you're using a different platform that's
great you can use other platforms with
our system as well we're not tied into
or locked into one system for people
that's one of the coolest things about
this is that when you can learn the
skills of how to be able to get more
sales and get more clients you can
dictate your paycheck you can decide how
much you want to work how you want to
show up and create the life that you
want I don't have to work more than 10
hours a week by Design and I've put it
together that way on purpose because
that's exactly the life that I want to
live and I want to show other people how
to do so as well all right this is
Jeremiah Kowski and I'll see you on our
next video we'll talk soon